An unlikely friendship. An incredible adventure.
The Wolf and the Lion is a family, adventure, drama
film directed by Gilles de Maistre.
After her grandfather's death, 20-year-old Alma decides to go back to her childhood
home - a little island in the heart of the majestic Canadian forest.
Whilst there, she rescues two helpless cubs: a wolf and a lion.
They forge an inseparable bond, but their world soon collapses as the
forest ranger discovers the animals and takes them away.
The two cub brothers must now embark on a treacherous journey across
Canada to be reunited with one another and Alma once more.
Alma, played by Molly Kunz.
Joe, played by Graham Greene.
Eli, played by Charlie Carrick.
Charles, played by Derek Johns.
Ysae, played by Rebecca Croll.
Rapha, played by Rhys Slack.
The Wolf and the Lion (French: Le loup et le lion) is a 2021 family adventure film directed by
Gilles de Maistre who also wrote the script with his wife Prune de Maistre.
The film stars Molly Kunz as Alma, who returns to her late grandfather's cabin and finds
herself taking care of a wolf pup and a lion cub who grow up together as brothers.
The film premiered on 25 September 2021 at the Zurich Film
Festival where it won best children's film.
It went on to wide release on 13 October 2021.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of canada, wolf, lion, animals, loving.
The tone is emotional.